<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Financial Assistant</string>
    <string name="signUp">Sign Up!</string>
    <string name="logIn">Log In</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="establishing_your_will">Establishing Your Will: You must first establish the document as your last and only will, which requires you to title your will as the “Last Will and Testament of (Your Full Legal Name).” Below this title, you should revoke any and all prior wills and codicils you previously executed, even if you never knowingly established a will in the past. Including such a statement prevents any confusion over other documents you have established, which may appear to be your will, from superseding your actual instructions.</string>
    <string name="appoint_administrators">Appoint Administrators: For most wills, the very next section is the appointment of the estate’s administrators. These are the individuals you appoint to assume the responsibility of managing and administering your estate. You should name at least one executor to oversee your estate, submit your will for probate and divide your assets among your beneficiaries according to your instructions. If you have a more complicated estate, or you want to assign different tasks to various administrators, you can appoint “task-specific” administrators with explicit instructions on what powers and responsibilities each administrator shall have. Whenever possible, name an alternate administrator to serve on your behalf if your first choice is unwilling or unable to serve. Otherwise, the court will appoint someone for your estate following state intestacy guidelines.</string>
    <string name="list_assets">List Assets: Your will should contain a list of your larger assets, such as real property, monetary interests and cash assets, including bank accounts. You should describe each individual asset as best you can, providing physical addresses, account numbers and passwords whenever possible. You should also list your personal property if you intend to bequeath it to a certain beneficiary. Anything not explicitly defined in your will and appropriately bequeathed to a named beneficiary will become a part of your estate’s residual assets, which is either given to one specific beneficiary or liquidated for the estate’s use, depending on your instructions.</string>
    <string name="name_beneficiaries">Name Beneficiaries: After describing your assets, the next section of your will should contain a list of your estate’s beneficiaries. These are the individuals or entities who will inherit your estate’s assets after your passing. You can bequeath specific property or cash amounts to each beneficiary however you desire, or assign a portion of your estate by percentage. When you are finished, name a beneficiary to inherit the residual assets; this beneficiary will receive everything that you did not bequeath to a specific beneficiary.</string>
    <string name="define_additional_instructions">Define Additional Instructions: In addition to the above, you can define any other instructions for the administration of your estate as needed. What you include directly relates to your personal circumstances - for example, if you have minor children, you would appoint a guardian to assume custody of your children and instructions for how they should be raised in your absence. You can define instructions for your funeral arrangements, arrange care for an elderly parent, establish a trust for your surviving relatives or include directives for just about any legal purpose.</string>
    <string name="tip1">1. Choose your card(s) carefully
Credit cards are not all alike, and you should choose the card(s) that best fit your needs and spending habits.</string>
    <string name="tip2">2. Only charge what you can afford
It might seem like an obvious piece of advice, but enough people ignore it to make it worth stressing.</string>
    <string name="tip3">3. Pay off your bills in full each month - and on time
If you only charge what you can afford, you\'ll be able to pay your credit card bills off in full each month - and you should absolutely do so.</string>
    <string name="tip4">4. Understand how dangerous debt can be
If you let any debt accumulate, it can take on a life of its own - especially when it's high-interest-rate debt.</string>
    <string name="tip5">5. Beware of fees
Credit card issuers rake in a lot of money from fees.</string>
    <string name="tip6">6. Don\'t just make minimum payments
If you end up with significant credit card debt at some point in your life, pay it off as quickly as you can.</string>
    <string name="tip7">7. Check your statements for problems
Take a minute to review all the charges. Are they all yours? If an identity thief has been using your credit card (or just the information on the card) to buy things, let the company know. </string>
    <string name="tip8">8. Don\'t be afraid to ask for breaks
Credit card contracts are full of terms and conditions and fine print, but don't assume they're all set in stone.</string>
    <string name="tip9">9. Keep an eye out for changes
Finally, remember that regulations on credit cards can and do change over time.</string>
    <string name="protip1">1. Keep Your Credit Utilization Low
Don’t max out your line of credit.</string>
    <string name="protip2">2. Use a Secured Credit Card to Build Your Credit
Using a credit card is an effective method to build your credit. If you don’t have credit yet, getting a loan is often difficult.</string>
    <string name="protip3">3. Pay Off Your Card Each Month to Maximize Rewards Value
If you get a rewards card, but carry a balance, the interest you pay will cancel out the rewards you earn.</string>
    <string name="protip4">4. Pay Off High-Interest Credit Cards First
Accumulating credit card debt with high-interest rates is bad debt that should be paid off fast.</string>
    <string name="protip5">5. Stay Away from Cash Advances
Credit cards should not be treated as a bank account that you can get cash from whenever you need it. </string>
    <string name="protip6">6. Use a Personal Finance App to Monitor Your Credit Usage
To help monitor and control your credit card usage, use a personal finance app on your cell phone that tracks, in real-time, your purchases by category.</string>
    <string name="protip7">7. Use Online Reporting from Your Credit Card to Monitor Spending Habits
It’s critical to keep track of your spending habits, control your expenses, and avoid getting into debt.</string>
    <string name="protip8">8. Don’t Share Credit Card Accounts with Your Spouse
There is usually minimal benefit to having multiple cardholders on one account. One partner can have spending problems, obtain limit increases, or incur debt, and the other partner will also be liable for this.</string>
    <string name="protip9">9. Be Careful with Promotional Offers
While some of these promotional offers may be beneficial to the users, you should still be careful and ensure you understand the terms thoroughly.</string>
    <string name="income">Income</string>
    <string name="incomeValue">$X,XXX.XX / Month</string>
    <string name="moneyHint">$00.00</string>
    <string name="addIncome">Add Income</string>
    <string name="removeIncome">Remove Income</string>
    <string name="expenseTitleTextview">Expenses</string>
    <string name="addExpense">Add Expense</string>
    <string name="removeExpense">Remove Expense</string>
    <string name="deposit">Deposit</string>
    <string name="withdraw">Withdraw</string>
    <string name="with_dep_hint">Deposit/Withdraw amount</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="budget">Budget</string>
    <string name="add_an_expense">Add a Monthly Expense:</string>
    <string name="expense_name">Expense name</string>
    <string name="brief_description">Brief description</string>
    <string name="incomes">Incomes</string>
    <string name="add_an_income">Add a monthly income:</string>
    <string name="add_income">Add a Monthly Income:</string>
    <string name="income_name">Income name</string>
    <string name="addIncome">Add Income</string>
    <string name="your_trends">Your Trends</string>
    <string name="trends_text_1">Viewing trends for past:</string>
</resources>
